Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
- Series IV Projects
  - Second Upgrade Project, Gregorian Feed
    - RSI/UAD Change Orders
      - Change Order #7, Cable Joint Redesign, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Change Order #8, Galvanize Tower Saddles, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Change Order #9, Tie Down Boom Diaphragms, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Change Order #10, Anchor 8 & 12 Excavation, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 53)
      - Change Order #11, A-4 Lateral Ext. 30 Degrees, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 54)
      - Change Order #12, A-12 Add'l Concrete, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 55)
      - Change Order #13, 3 Misc. FFP Quotes for Out-of-Scope Work, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 56)
      - Change Order #14, Cabler Spacers, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 57)
      - Change Order #15, Heat Exchangers w/ Grating, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 58)
      - Change Order #16, Change in Dome Diameter, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 59)
      - Change Order #17, Addition of Hatches to Dome, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 60)
      - Authorization to Proceed with #15 & 17, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 61)
      - Change Order #18, Weep Holes, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 62)
      - Change Order #19, Revisions to Dome Collar Design, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 63)
      - Change Order #20, Feed Module Modifications, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 64)
      - Change Order #21, U bolts (Withdrawn) - no folder (Box 34)
      - Change Order #22, Ballast Platform Redesign (Box 34, Folder 65)
      - Change Order #23, Panel Installation (Box 34, Folder 66)
      - Change Order #24, Drives System Concept (Box 34, Folder 67)
      - Change Order #25, Credit Proposal for Platforms, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Change Order #26, Delete Platform Anodizing & Add Hand Rail, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Change Order #27, Reduction of Quantity of Azimuth Trolley Gears, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Change Order 28, Backup Structure & Panel Installation, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Change Order #29, Dome Truss, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Change Order #30, Monorail Addition for Collar Truss, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Change Order #31, Chafing Plate Redesign, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Change Order #32, Finish Requirements, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Change Order #33, Add'l Fencing Around Anchors A8 & A12, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Change Order #34, Elimination of Machined Rings, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Change Order #35, Machine Work by Temcor, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Change Order #36, Subreflector Target Installation, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Change Order #37, Steel Frame for Temporary EL Drive System, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Change Order #38, Photogrammetric Services, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Change Order #39, Installation of Feed Module Camrol Race, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Change Order #40, Relocation of Cable Dampeners, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Change Order #41, Dome Rigging Redesign, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Change Order #42, Field Drilling of Weep Holes in Outriggers & Application of Zinc Rich Compound, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Change Order #43, Task Schedule Revision, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Change Order #44, Modification of Gregorian Trolley Wheel Shafts, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Change Order #45, Calibration of Cable Jacking System, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Change Order #46, Confirmation of Tension in Aux. Backstay Cables, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Change Order #47, Gregorian Survival Pins, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Change Order #48, Rework of Elevation Rail Shim & Washer Plates, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Change Order #49, Rework of Azimuth Track, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Change Order #50, Compensation for Downtime, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Change Order #51 (Withdrawn) - no folder (Box 35)
      - Change Order #52, Elevation Rail Shimblocks, Refabrication & Installation, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Change Order #53, Radial Adjustment of Azimuth Rail, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Change Order #54, Delays Due to Damage at the T8 Hairpin, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Change Order #55, Revisions to Tensioning Table, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - NSF Audit of COMSAT/RSI Change Orders, Aug 1994 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - RSI-Follow-up Briefing on Status Gregorian Upgrading, Nov 1994 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - RSI CQC Progress Reports, 7/21/93-6/21/94 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - RSI CQC Progress Reports, 6/22/94-6/22/95 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - RSI CQC Progress Reports, 6/23/95-12/14/95 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - RSI CQC Progress Reports, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Feasibility Study & Concept Development for Extension of Reflector, 10/80 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Condition Survey Report on the Suspended Antenna Structure at Arecibo Observatory, 11/82 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Ammann & Whitney (A&W)
      - Gregorian Feasibility Study, 12/86 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Arecibo Mini Inspection, May 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Hanger Inspections 1989-90 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Owner/Engineer Agreement (Conceptual Design Services), Mar 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Owner/Engineer Agreement (Detailed Engineering Design Services), Nov 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Arecibo Radio Telescope 1991 Inspection Results, 1/92 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Feed Arm Truss, Book 1, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Feed Arm Truss, Book 2, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Gregorian Structural System Calculations, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Technical Specifications & List of Drawings for Gregorian Upgrading, July 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1992 Upgrading Platform Maintenace Report, J. Maldonado (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - A&W Pre-Proposal Documents, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - A&W Invoices #1-16, June 1991-Sept 1992 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - A&W Invoices #17-32, Oct 1992-Mar 1994 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - A&W Invvoices #33-41, Apr-Dec 1994 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - A&W Invoices #42-60, Mar 1995-July 1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - A&W Invoices #61-74, July 1996-Nov 1997 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - A&W Invoices #75-79, Dec 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - A&W Invoices #80-84, May 1998-May-1999 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Presentation of 95% Complete Design/Drawings, May 1992 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Change Orders #1-3, Nov 1992-July 1994 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Change Order #4, May 1995 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Change Order #5, Jan 1996 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Change Order #6, May 1996 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Change Order #7, Sept 1996 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Change Order #8, Feb 1997 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Change Order #9, May 1997 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Change Order #10, July 1997 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Change Order #11, Jan 1998 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Amendment No. 12 to Contract 92.231, Oct 1998 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - A&W Dunn & Bradstreet Report, 2-26-96 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - A&W Budgets, 1988-1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - A&W-Cornell Facilities Job Orders, 7/91-1/07 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - The Second Arecibo Upgrade, Paul Goldsmith, IEEE Potentials article, Aug/Sep 1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Gregorian Analysis Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Structural Condition Survey, 5/03 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Analysis of Suspended Platform Weight & Main Cable Tensions, 8/06 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Structural Condition Survey, 3/11 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Vertex Servo Drive System
      - Drive System General (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Quality Assurance Manual, Vol. II, March 1993 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Servo Drive Systems Specification, Nov 1994 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Drive System, List of Prospective Proposers, Jan 1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Drive System RFP, Jan 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Drive System, Addenda, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Drive System Vertex Proposal, Vol. I & II, 3/16/95 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Drive System,COMSAT-RSI Proposal, 3-17-95 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Drive System, Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Drive System On-Site Reports, 1996-97 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Drive System, Vertex Corres. Pre-Contract 1995 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Vertex Correspondence Post Award, 1995-97 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Final Azimuth Design Drawings, Sep 1995 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Drive System P.O., 1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Drive System Design/Procurement Telecon Meeting Minutes, 1995-96 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Drive System Quality Control Plan, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Drive System Final Design Review, July 1995 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Drive System Post Award Conference Minutes, 5/16/95 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - LAN Interface Description, Rev. 2.1, June 1995 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Drive System Final Design Report, Oct 1995 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Drive System, Import Tax, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Drive System, Change Orders 1-3 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Drive System, Change Order 7 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Drive System, Change Order 9 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Drive System, Change Order 12 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Payments (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Servo Drive System Upgrade, Acceptance Test Plan, May 1996 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Servo Drive System Upgrade, Acceptance Test Plan, Rev. 1.1, 7/96 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 6/94-7/95 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 7/95-12/95 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1/96-6/01 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Carriage House Encoders-Instruction Manual (B. Sisk, 2/92) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Carriage House Drive System-Instruction Manual (J. Hagen, 7/88) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Azimuth Drive System-Instruction Manual (E. Torres & J. Hagen, 9/86) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Gregorian Swart Consulting
      - Gregory Swart Consulting Agreement, rotary floor drive, Apr 1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Gregory Swart Consulting Agreement, Amendment #1&2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Gregory Swart Payments, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Gregory Swart Tertiary Mount Agreement, Oct 1995 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Gregory Swart Payments, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Ben Parvin Consulting
      - Ben Parvin Consulting Agreement, drive & control system, Aug 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Ben Parvin Payments, 1995-97 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Azimuth Track Height Adjustments, 1996-97 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Platform Weight/Height Changes, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Elevation Rail Surveying & Alignment Procedure, Apr 1997 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Monitor & Control Systems, 1992-93 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - IF/LO System, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Drawing Control
      - RSI Drawing Fabrication Schedule, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Submittals/Cover Letters #1, 1993-96 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Submittals/Cover Letters #2, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Drawing Transmittals, 1994-97 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Punch Lists, 1995-97 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Engineering Change Requests, 1995-96 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Slotted Hole Catalogs 1995-96 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Field Modification Reports, 1995-97 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Misc. Drawing Efforts, 1994-96 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Temcor Drawings, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Praeger Kavanaugh (EL Drive Assembly), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Bethlehem Steel (Rack Gear), 1962 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - CEC (Dome/Pump Interfaces), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Engineered Gear Systems (Rotary gloor reduc. Gear), 1995-96 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Roads, Bulidings, Sq. Ft. & Parking Areas, 4/06 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - AO Property Map, 3/94 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Nogama Construction, Anchor work, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Paul Stetson, mini-Gregorian May 1986, May 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Upgrade Completion Commissioning Phase, 1997-98 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Dome tilt, 1997-98 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Early Observing, 1997-98 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Cable U-bolt Cut, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Elevation Rails, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Subreflector Panel Project
      - Stetson's Search for Panel Manufacturers, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - General, 1993-96 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Cornell Contract's Management, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - General Bidding Process, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Request for Proposal, 2-18-94 & Corres. (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Addendum Inquiries & Addenda 1-3, Apr 1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Proposal Evaluation Committee, Apr 1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Meetings with RSI & ESSCO, May 1994 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - 1st Technical Clarification Responses from RSI & ESSCO, 5-06-94 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - ESSCO Revised Pricing in Response to Post-Proposal Bulletins, 5/94 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Procurement Summary, 8/94 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - ESSCO Technical Proposal to provide panels for the Arecibo Observatory subreflector, 6/24/94 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Letter of Intent to RSI, 8/03/94 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - RSI Cert. of Current Cost or Pricing Data, Dec 1994 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - RSI Proposal for Subreflector Panels Project Arecibo Observatory Upgrade, 4/12/94 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - RSI Cost Proposal for Subreflector Panels Project Arecibo Observatory Upgrade, 4/12/94 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - RSI Cost Proposal for Subreflector Panels Project Arecibo Observatory Upgrade, Addendum 1, 6/24/94 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - RSI Proposal for Subreflector Panels Project Arecibo Observatory Upgrade, Addendum 1, 6/24/94 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - RSI Cost Proposal for Subreflector Panels Project Arecibo Observatory Upgrade, Best & Final Offer, 8/01/94 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - RSI Clarification & Discussion Meeting, 5/17/94 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Post-Proposal Bulletins, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - RSI Correspondence, 1993-96 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - RSI Payments, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - RSI Test Results, Sep 1995 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Purchase Order Nov 1995 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Schedules, 1995-95 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Tertiary Reflector System
      - Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - COMSAT-RSI Response to Statement of Work Tertiary Reflector System, 5-06-95 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - COMSAT-RSI Arecibo Upgrade Tertiary Subreflector Final Design Review, 11-29-95 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Change Orders, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Backup Structure
      - Request for Proposal, 9-21-94 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - COMSAT-RSI Subreflector Backup Structure Proposal, 9-26-94 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - COMSAT-RSI Revised Adjustable Panel Support Quote, 1-04-94 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - COMSAT-RSI Letter of Intent, 10-13-94 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Report by Joe Vellozzi (Ammann & Whitney) on RSI Proposal, 10/94 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Funding Correspondence, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Procurement Summary, Oct 1994 (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - Purchase Order to COMSAT-RSI, Oct 1994 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - COMSAT-RSI Correspondence, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - COMSAT-RSI Quality Control Plan, 4-14-95 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - S-Band Transmitter Upgrade Project
    - S-Band Transmitter Upgrade correspondence
      - S-Band Corres. 1986-1993 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - S-Band Corres. Jan-Feb 1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - S-Band Corres. Mar-May 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - S-Band Corres. June-Dec 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - S-Band Corres. Jan 1995-Oct 1999 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Arecibo Observatory S-Band Radar Program, D.B. Campbell, 7/86 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Cornell Facilities - RFP Corres., 1992-93 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Sponsored Programs - RFP Corres., 1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Project Schedules, 1992-95 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Meetings, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Site Reports, Feb-Oct 1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Facilities Job Orders, 1/94-7/95 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - S-Band Transmitter RFP
      - Request for Proposal, 3/28/93 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Addenda 1-3, Apr-May 1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Pre-Proposal Conference, 4-15-93 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - RFP & Proposal Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Proposal Evaluation, June 1993 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Continental Electronics (CEC)
      - Arecibo Upgrade Study, Apr 1989 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Engineering Service Agreement, Sept 1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - S-Band Transmitter Upgrade Study, Dec 1989 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project, Item 1a, Base Proposal, 3/93 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project, Item 1b, Technical Proposal, 3/93 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Addenda 1-4, Apr-May 1993 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Clarification Meetings, July-Aug 1993 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project, Revision 1, July 1993 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project, Revision 2, Aug 1993 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Contract, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Action Items from Pre-Construction Work Meeting, Oct 18-19, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project, Intermediate Program Review, Dec 1993 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Press Release, 10/8/93 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Bond/Insurance Info Status, 1993-97 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Quality Control Plan, Oct 1993 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - S-Band Transmitter Project Third Program Review, June 1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Project Schedules, 1993-95 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Revised Schedule of Values, Nov 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Invoices & Payment, Nov 1993-June 1995 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Invoices & Payment, July 1995-Sept 1997 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Monthly Project Reports, Dec 1994-Dec 1996 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Factory Acceptance Test Procedure, Jan 1996 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Change Order #1, Jan 1995 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Change Order #2, Feb 1995 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Change Order #3, July 1996 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Change Order #4, Oct 1996 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Change Order #5, Nov 1996 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Change Order #6, Jan 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - S-Band Budgets, 1993-95 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Cash Flow, 1993-95 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - General Electric 1993-94 Inductrol purchase, Corres. 1993-94 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Varian/Continental Elec. 1990-1994
      - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Klystron quotation & procurement, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Klystron specifications, 1972, 1982, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - S-Band Transmitter Upgrade Study for the Arecibo Observatory, 1/90 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Taitem Engineering, 1994-1995
      - Taitem Engineering Services Agreement, March 1994 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Taitem Engineering, Request for payments 1994-95 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Meeting Minutes, Mar-Oct 1994 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Progress Reports, May-Oct 1994 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Memos, May-Nov 1994 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Prime Power RFP & Correspondence, 1992-1994
      - RFP Diesel Fuel Gas Turbine Generating System, Oct 1993 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Proposal Evaluation & Corres., 1992-94 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Addenda 1-3, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Solar Turbines, 1993-2003
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Arecibo Turbine Generator - Job Meeting Minutes, 4/94-12/95 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Solar Turbines Turbomachinery Proposal,Dec 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Solar Turbines Turbomachinery Revised Proposal, Jan 1995 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Equipment Test Plan for Refurbished Generator Set, 8/94 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Torsional Rotordynamic Analysis of the Solar/Arecibo Turbo-Generator Set - Final Report, 9-15-94 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Torsional Transient Analysis of the Revised Solar/Arecibo Turbo-Generator Set, 11-14-94 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Terms & Conditions/Negotiations, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Purchase Order, May 1995 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Transient Torsional & Lateral Analysis of Centaur Generator Set, 10-26-98 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Goldsmith Files-430 MHz, 1993-2000
      - 430 MHz B-B Transmitter, 1995-2000 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - 430 MHz Waveguide, 1993-95 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Klystrons, 1993-94 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - 430 MHz System, 1993-98 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - 430 MHz Dual Beam, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - 430 MHz Rx Protection, 1993-95 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Transmitter radiation levels, 1997-98 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Emergency Generator, 1992-1998
      - RFP -Diesel Engine Generating Set, Aug 1995 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Bidder Selection, Oct 1995 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Syracuse Supply Co - Caterpillar quotation, Sept 1995 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Syracuse Supply Co - Bill of Material, Jan 1996 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Syracuse Supply Co. - Corres. 1995-96 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - High Voltage Power Supply Building (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Maury Microwave - Switches refurbishment, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Los Alamos 430 MHz Klystrons, 1992-93 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - S-Band License, Dec 1993 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Ambient Impact Assessment, EPA, Emissions, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Entropy Inc. - Emissions Compliance Testing, Jan 1997 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Rotary Coupler Design (Hagen), 6-6-94 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Turnstile Junction, 10/93 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Hybrid Combiner, 5/93 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Rotary Joint, 12/93 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Monitor & Control interface to S-Band transmitter controller, 11/92 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - 2380 MHz HP8660 Synthesizer, 5/93 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - S-Band cooling system, 4/93 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - S-Band FAA Safety, 8/98 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Radio Frequency Interference (RFI), 1984-2003
      - General Correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      - General Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - RFI Issues, June 1960 - May 1991 (Box 42, Folder 37)
      - RFI Issues, Aug-Dec 1991 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - RFI Issues, Jan 1992-Dec 1994 (Box 42, Folder 39)
      - RFI Issues, May 1995-March 2002 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      - RFI Issues, June 2002-Sept 2003 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - S-Band Radar Receiver Technical Report, E. Lauria, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Ground Screen Project
    - Stetson - Preliminary Cost Estimate for Ground Screen, June 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Ground Screen cost estimate and engineering review,( TIW Systems), Oct 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Ground Screen RFP
      - RFP & Addenda, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Bid Process, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence 1990-92 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1993-94 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Projected Funding & Expenditures, 1993-94 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Meetings, 1991-93 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Punch Lists, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Schedules, 1991-92 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - M. Davis - Correction to the 1986 Prediction of Ground Screen Spillover Noise, 3/29/94 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Progress Reports, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Cornell Facilities Job Orders, 1/91-8/94 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Contemporary Constructors, Inc. (CCI)
      - Design/Build Contract, 2-25-92 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - CCI Site Meetings (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - CCI Payments (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Change Orders (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Drawings
      - Panel drawing, Cutler-Gallaway Services, 10/92 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Clutter screen, Ron Woodman, 1/80 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Goldsmith Files, 1991